[
    {"id": 1, "question": "What is Capital City of England ?", "options":["Manchester", "Leeds", "Cambridge", "London"], "correct-answer":"London"},
    {"id": 2, "question": "What are the 4 countries in UK ?", "options":["England, Northern Ireland, Wales and Scotland","England, Shetland, Wales and Scotland", "England, Shetland, Wales and Orkney", "Glassgow, Wales, England and Ireland"], 
    "correct-answer":"England, Northern Ireland, Wales and Scotland"},
    {"id": 3, "question": "What is UK's current approximate population ?", "options":["Manchester", "Leeds", "Cambridge", "London"], "correct-answer":"London"},
    {"id": 4, "question": "Select the city in England that has an eroding coast ? ", "options":["Manchester", "Happisburgh", "Cambridge", "London"], "correct-answer":"Happisburgh"},
    {"id": 5, "question": "What are the 4 oceans that surrounds UK ?", "options":["North Atlantic Ocean, North Sea, Irish Sea and Pacific Ocean", 
    "North Sea, North Atlantic Ocean, Arctic Ocean and Pacific Ocean","North Sea, North Atlantic Ocean, English Channel and Irish Sea", "North Atlantic Ocean, Arctic Ocean, Pacific Ocean and Southern Ocean"], 
    "correct-answer":"North Sea, North Atlantic Ocean, English Channel and Irish Sea"},
    {"id": 6, "question": "What year did UK joined world war I ?", "options":["1930", "1945", "1920", "1914"], "correct-answer":"1914"},
    {"id": 7, "question": "When was the Tudor period ? ", "options":["1485-1603", "1484-1602", "1483-1605", "1481-1610"], "correct-answer":"1485-1603"},
    {"id": 8, "question": "What year did Henry VIII became king of England ?", "options":["1513", "1506", "1512", "1509"], "correct-answer": "1509"},
    {"id": 9, "question": "Who is the father of Queen Elizabeth I ?", "options":["Jacob VI", "Henry VIII", "Authur VII", "James II"], "correct-answer":"Henry VIII"},
    {"id": 10, "question": "When was the Stuart period ? ", "options":["1610-1715", "1604-1715", "1603-1714", "1605-1714"], "correct-answer":"1603-1714"},
    {"id": 11, "question": "What religion do a large fraction of UK follow ? ", "options":["Christianity", "Sikhism", "Islam", "Judaism"], "correct-answer":"Christianity"},
    {"id": 12, "question": "What are the festivals in Christianity ? ", "options":["Christmas and Easter", "Christmas and Easter Sunday", "Good Friday, Easter and Christmas", "Palm Sunday, Good Friday, Easter and Christmas"], "correct-answer":"Christmas and Easter"},
    {"id": 13, "question": "What are the pilgrimage places for Christianity? ", "options":["Church of England", "Lourdes and Iona", "Lourdes", "Iona"], "correct-answer":"Lourdes and Iona"},
    {"id": 14, "question": "What is the symbol of Christianity", "options":["Cross", "Sword", "Lion", "Knight"], "correct-answer":"London"},
    {"id": 15, "question": "In year 2025, what date is Easter ?", "options":["21st April 2025", "22nd April 2025", "18th April 2025", "20th April 2025"], "correct-answer":"20th April 2025"},
    {"id": 16, "question": "In the year 2018, what was the popular music genre in UK?", "options":["Pop", "Jazz", "Oprah", "Rock"], "correct-answer":"Pop"},
    {"id": 17, "question": "What is the name of the traditional instrument of England ? ", "options":["Flute", "Drum", "Pipe/Tabor", "Gituar"], "correct-answer":"Pipe/Tabor"},
    {"id": 18, "question": "Which artist was born in the UK ?", "options":["Levro Deculley", "Jacob Robbinson", "Harry Styles", "Kate McKanny"], "correct-answer":"Harry Styles"},
    {"id": 19, "question": "Which music TV show is based in UK ? ", "options":["Country Music Festival", "British Music Vibes", "Music Festive ball London", "Eurovision"], "correct-answer":"London"},
    {"id": 20, "question": "Which city was Adele born ?", "options":["London", "Cambridge", "Oxford", "Exeter"], "correct-answer":"London"}


]
